[
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifz",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a kind of court of the United States?",
    "question_zh": "以下哪项不是美国的法院类型？",
    "options": [
      "A. the national court",
      "B. the Supreme Court",
      "C. the court of appeals",
      "D. the district courts"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. the national court"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgico",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "There are currently ________ district courts in the United States.",
    "question_zh": "目前美国共有________个地区法院。",
    "options": [
      "A. 52",
      "B. 54",
      "C. 92",
      "D. 94"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. 94"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgii5",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "There are currently _______ courts of appeals in the United States.",
    "question_zh": "目前美国共有________个上诉法院。",
    "options": [
      "A. 10",
      "B. 11",
      "C. 12",
      "D. 13"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. 12"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifl",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "District judgeships are filled by the President with the consent of _________.",
    "question_zh": "地区法官职位由总统任命，但需获得________的同意。",
    "options": [
      "A. Chief Justice of Supreme Court",
      "B. Attorney General",
      "C. the Senate",
      "D. the House of Representatives"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. the Senate"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi3o",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Generally, the trial or petit jury consists of _______ ordinary citizens.",
    "question_zh": "通常，陪审团由________名普通公民组成。",
    "options": [
      "A. 1-6",
      "B. 6-12",
      "C. 12-23",
      "D. 23-30"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. 6-12"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi7b",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Generally, the grand jury consists of _______ ordinary citizens.",
    "question_zh": "通常，大陪审团由________名普通公民组成。",
    "options": [
      "A. 1-6",
      "B. 6-12",
      "C. 12-23",
      "D. 23-30"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. 12-23"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkginh",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The Supreme Court consists of a chief justice and _______ associate justices.",
    "question_zh": "美国最高法院由1位首席大法官和________位大法官组成。",
    "options": [
      "A. 7",
      "B. 8",
      "C. 9",
      "D. 10"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. 8"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgihk",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In the United States, people between the ages of _______ are the most inclined age group to commit crimes.",
    "question_zh": "在美国，岁年龄段的人群犯罪倾向最高。",
    "options": [
      "A. 11-19",
      "B. 19-24",
      "C. 24-45",
      "D. 45-54"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. 11-19"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgibc",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT considered when the aids of public services are given?",
    "question_zh": "在提供公共服务援助时，以下哪项不被考虑？",
    "options": [
      "A. Income",
      "B. dependent family members",
      "C. employment situation",
      "D. location of residence"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. location of residence"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi7e",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The US didn’t set up a social security system on a national level until the Social Security Act passed in __.",
    "question_zh": "美国直到《社会保障法》于________年通过后，才在全国范围内建立了社会保障体系。",
    "options": [
      "A. 1864",
      "B. 1929",
      "C. 1935",
      "D. 1945"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. 1935"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkginu",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The United States ranks ________ in the world in the total value of its economic production.",
    "question_zh": "按经济产出总值计算，美国位居世界。",
    "options": [
      "A. first",
      "B. second",
      "C. third",
      "D. Fourth"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. first"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgimp",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The following are the factors that have contributed to the development of the U.S. economy EXCEPT .",
    "question_zh": "以下因素均促进了美国经济发展，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. the vast space and resources of the land",
      "B. continuous influx of immigrants",
      "C. English as its national language",
      "D. a powerful financial market"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. English as its national language"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi4r",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "What is America’s most important food crop?",
    "question_zh": "美国最重要的粮食作物是什么？",
    "options": [
      "A. Corn.",
      "B. Rice.",
      "C. Barley.",
      "D. Oat."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Corn."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgimz",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Service industries account for more than _________ of the U.S. gross domestic product.",
    "question_zh": "服务业占美国国内生产总值的比重超过________。",
    "options": [
      "A. a third",
      "B. half",
      "C. two thirds",
      "D. three fourth"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. three fourth"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkginq",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The American South is a center of the following traditional crops EXCEPT .",
    "question_zh": "美国南部是以下传统农作物的中心产区，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. tobacco",
      "B. corn",
      "C. cotton",
      "D. wheat"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. wheat"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiji",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In the United States, the following areas tend to specialize in high-tech and computer industries EXCEPT .",
    "question_zh": "在美国，以下地区通常专注于高科技和计算机产业，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. Northeast",
      "B. Midwest",
      "C. Northwest",
      "D. Southwest"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Midwest"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi82",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "After World War I, the world's financial center has transformed from _____ to.",
    "question_zh": "第一次世界大战后，世界金融中心从________转移至________。",
    "options": [
      "A. New York",
      "Washington D. C.",
      "B. London",
      "New York",
      "C. London",
      "Paris",
      "D. Paris",
      "New York"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. London; New York"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiiz",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The monopolies of the US automobile industry are the following EXCEPT.",
    "question_zh": "美国汽车行业的垄断企业包括以下，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. Ford Motors",
      "B. General Motors",
      "C. BMW",
      "D. Chrysler"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. BMW"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi3v",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the followings is NOT true about the US economy?",
    "question_zh": "关于美国经济，以下哪项表述不正确？",
    "options": [
      "A. The economic system of the US is largely a market-oriented economy.",
      "B. The agriculture industry of the US is not well organized.",
      "C. The American economy is based largely on a free enterprise system.",
      "D. The US economy is highly diversified."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. The agriculture industry of the US is not well organized."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiah",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which is NOT included in service industry?",
    "question_zh": "以下哪项不属于服务业？",
    "options": [
      "A. Banking.",
      "B. Management consultation.",
      "C. Insurance",
      "D. Steelmaking."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Steelmaking."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgikp",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The United States produces as much as half of the world's.",
    "question_zh": "美国生产了全球________产量的一半。",
    "options": [
      "A. wheat and rice",
      "B. soybeans and corn",
      "C. tobacco and vegetable oil",
      "D. cotton"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. soybeans and corn"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgimh",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT factor contributed to the development of industry in the US?",
    "question_zh": "以下哪项不是促进美国工业发展的因素？",
    "options": [
      "A. diversified ethnic groups",
      "B. abundant resources",
      "C. vast market",
      "D. innovated technology"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. diversified ethnic groups"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgife",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The president in the US can serve _____ term(s).",
    "question_zh": "美国总统可连任________届。",
    "options": [
      "A. one",
      "B. two",
      "C. three",
      "D. four"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. two"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi42",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which branch of the American government has the power to interpret the Constitution?",
    "question_zh": "美国政府中，哪个部门拥有解释宪法的权力？",
    "options": [
      "A. The President.",
      "B. The House.",
      "C. The Senate.",
      "D. The Supreme Court."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. The Supreme Court."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiex",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "American Presidents are elected.",
    "question_zh": "美国总统由________选举产生。",
    "options": [
      "A. every two years",
      "B. every four years",
      "C. every five years",
      "D. every six years"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. every four years"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgir2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about the Supreme Court of the US?",
    "question_zh": "关于美国最高法院，以下哪项表述不正确？",
    "options": [
      "A. It is the highest court of the United States.",
      "B. It has no power to interpret the Constitution.",
      "C. It consists of a chief justice and eight associate justices.",
      "D. It determines whether legislation or executive acts conform to the Constitution."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. It has no power to interpret the Constitution."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgidp",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In the US, the heads of the various executive departments from a council of advisers are generally known as the President's.",
    "question_zh": "在美国，各行政部门首长组成的顾问委员会通常被称为总统的________。",
    "options": [
      "A. Advisory Group",
      "B. Executive Office",
      "C. Special Commission",
      "D. Cabinet"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Cabinet"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifc",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Abraham Lincoln, as candidate of, was elected President in 1860.",
    "question_zh": "1860年，作为________候选人的亚伯拉罕·林肯当选总统。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Democratic Party",
      "B. the Republican Party",
      "C. the Labor Party",
      "D. the Conservative Party"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. the Republican Party"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi1q",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The US President has a lot of powers, EXCEPT the power to.",
    "question_zh": "美国总统拥有诸多权力，但不包括________的权力。",
    "options": [
      "A. veto any bill passed by Congress",
      "B. appoint federal judges when vacancies occur",
      "C. make laws",
      "D. issue regulations and directives regarding the work of the federal departments"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. make laws"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiqb",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Each state in the US is entitled to _____ senators.",
    "question_zh": "美国每个州有权选出________名参议员。",
    "options": [
      "A. three",
      "B. four",
      "C. two",
      "D. five"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. two"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgip2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "How many seats does the Senate of the Congress of the Unites States have?",
    "question_zh": "美国国会参议院共有多少个席位？",
    "options": [
      "A. 100.",
      "B. 345.",
      "C. 435.",
      "D. 534."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. 100."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi2v",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The two major parties today have ______ differences in policy concentration.",
    "question_zh": "当今两大政党的政策重点存在________差异。",
    "options": [
      "A. no",
      "B. little",
      "C. some",
      "D. great"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. some"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgif6",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The writers of the Constitution worked out the checks and balances in order to _______.",
    "question_zh": "宪法起草者设计制衡机制的目的是________。",
    "options": [
      "A. prevent the government from misusing its power",
      "B. prevent the government from being strong",
      "C. pacify those who opposed the Constitution",
      "D. meet the demands of small states"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. prevent the government from misusing its power"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi56",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The President of the United States is elected _____.",
    "question_zh": "美国总统由________选举产生。",
    "options": [
      "A. indirectly by the electors",
      "B. by Congress",
      "C. directly by the voters",
      "D. None of the above."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. None of the above."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgip2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "________ has the power to elect the U.S. President in Electoral College deadlocks .",
    "question_zh": "若选举人团僵持不下，有权选举美国总统。",
    "options": [
      "A. the House of Representatives",
      "B. the Senate",
      "C. the Cabinet",
      "D. the Supreme Court"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. the House of Representatives"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgim6",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The Supreme Court of the United States consists of one Chief Justice and ______ Associate Justices.",
    "question_zh": "美国最高法院由1位首席大法官和________位大法官组成。",
    "options": [
      "A. 6",
      "B. 7",
      "C. 8",
      "D. 10"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. 8"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi1y",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The U.S. Congress has the power to override the president’s veto by a _____ majority.",
    "question_zh": "美国国会可通过________多数票推翻总统的否决。",
    "options": [
      "A. 2/3",
      "B. 3/4",
      "C. 3/5",
      "D. 4/5"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. 2/3"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgib8",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The current situation of African-Americans presents _______.",
    "question_zh": "当前非裔美国人的现状表现为。",
    "options": [
      "A. a favorable picture",
      "B. a negative picture",
      "C. a mixed picture",
      "D. a positive picture"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. a mixed picture"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi2b",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Although discrimination has been legally abolished, ________.",
    "question_zh": "尽管法律上已废除歧视，但________。",
    "options": [
      "A. discrimination in employment still exists",
      "B. discrimination in university admission still exists",
      "C. poverty rate of the blacks is the highest among all racial and ethnic groups",
      "D. inequality and subtle discrimination still exist"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. inequality and subtle discrimination still exist"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi7d",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Now about 80% to 90% of immigration to the United States is from _______.",
    "question_zh": "如今，约80%至90%的美国移民来自________。",
    "options": [
      "A. Asian and Hispanic countries",
      "B. African countries",
      "C. European countries",
      "D. Central and South American countries"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Asian and Hispanic countries"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkginy",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Some people say Asian-Americans owe their success to the Asian tradition of the following EXCEPT ________.",
    "question_zh": "有人认为亚裔美国人的成功归功于亚洲传统，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. family",
      "B. hard work",
      "C. education",
      "D. discrimination"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. discrimination"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgipp",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The first immigrants in American history came from ______.",
    "question_zh": "美国历史上首批移民来自________。",
    "options": [
      "A. England and the Netherlands",
      "B. Ireland",
      "C. West Germany",
      "D. East Europe"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. England and the Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgios",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Among the major Hispanic groups in the United States, the largest group is .",
    "question_zh": "在美国主要的西班牙裔群体中，人数最多的是________。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Puerto Ricans",
      "B. the Mexican-Americans",
      "C. the Cuban-Americans",
      "D. the Central and South American immigrants"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. the Mexican-Americans"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi9p",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The Native Americans are .",
    "question_zh": "美洲原住民是________。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Indians",
      "B. the whites",
      "C. the blacks",
      "D. the Hispanics"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. the Indians"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkginn",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "People often describe the characteristics of American population with the following terms EXCEPT* .",
    "question_zh": "人们常用以下术语描述美国人口特征，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. Melting pot",
      "B. Salad bowl",
      "C. Pizza",
      "D. Spaghetti"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Spaghetti"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgini",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The largest of the racial and ethnic minorities in the US is *********.",
    "question_zh": "美国最大规模的种族和族裔少数群体是________。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Indians",
      "B. the Japanese",
      "C. the Chinese",
      "D. the Hispanics"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. the Hispanics"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgihx",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The United States is the******** most populous nation in the world.",
    "question_zh": "美国是世界________人口大国。",
    "options": [
      "A. the first",
      "B. the second",
      "C. the third",
      "D. the fourth"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. the third"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgip5",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The most densely populated region is the _________ part of the country.",
    "question_zh": "人口最稠密的地区是该国的________部分。",
    "options": [
      "A. western",
      "B. southern",
      "C. northeastern",
      "D. southwestern"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. northeastern"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgie2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Today, __________ are one of the fastest growing minorities in America due to immigration (legal and illegal) and higher birth rates.",
    "question_zh": "如今，由于移民（包括合法与非法）和较高出生率，________已成为美国增长最快的少数群体之一。",
    "options": [
      "A. Asian Americans",
      "B. American Indians",
      "C. the Whites",
      "D. Hispanics"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Hispanics"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgip0",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "At present, ___________ have come to be viewed as a “model minority”; several of them have won Nobel Prizes.",
    "question_zh": "目前，________被视为“模范少数族裔”；其中多人已获诺贝尔奖。",
    "options": [
      "A. Asian Americans",
      "B. American Indians",
      "C. the Whites",
      "D. Hispanics"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Asian Americans"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgicj",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "_______________ are people who came to the New World prior to the founding of the US.",
    "question_zh": "________是指在美国建国前抵达新大陆的人群。",
    "options": [
      "A. Early Immigrants",
      "B. New Immigrants",
      "C. Old Immigrants",
      "D. Late Immigrants"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Early Immigrants"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi12",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "__________ and Texas are the most populous states, which means the center of American population has shifted westward and southward.",
    "question_zh": "_和得克萨斯州是人口最多的州，表明美国人口重心已向西和向南转移。",
    "options": [
      "A. Florida",
      "B. California",
      "C. New York State",
      "D. New Jersey"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. California"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgice",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The Union Army under the command of _____ defeated the Confederate Army at Gettysburg, Pennsylvania during the Civil War.",
    "question_zh": "内战期间，指挥的联邦军队在宾夕法尼亚州葛底斯堡击败了邦联军队。",
    "options": [
      "A. Abraham Lincoln",
      "B. Ulysses S. Grant",
      "C. Robert E. Lee",
      "D. Andrew Jackson"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Ulysses S. Grant"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgijw",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In September 1783. Britain and the US signed the, which marked the independence of the United States.",
    "question_zh": "1783年9月，英国与美国签署《》，标志着美国独立。",
    "options": [
      "A. Treaty of Paris",
      "B. Declaration of Independence",
      "C. Articles of Confederation",
      "D. Great Compromise of July 16"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Treaty of Paris"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi70",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following statements does NOT properly describe the Progressive Movement of the early 20th century?",
    "question_zh": "以下哪项未能准确描述20世纪初的进步运动？",
    "options": [
      "A. The movement required both political and military efforts.",
      "B. The movement demanded a series of social reforms.",
      "C. The movement was not an organized campaign with clearly defined goals.",
      "D. The movement started at the “grass roots” level."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. The movement required both political and military efforts."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi92",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following US Presidents was in power when the Great Depression just took place in 1929?",
    "question_zh": "1929年大萧条爆发时，哪位美国总统在任？",
    "options": [
      "A. Herbert C. Hoover.",
      "B. Calvin Coolidge.",
      "C. Franklin Roosevelt.",
      "D. Warren G. Harding."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Herbert C. Hoover."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiqk",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "started the New Deal program to get the United States out of the Great Depression.",
    "question_zh": "启动了“新政”计划以帮助美国摆脱大萧条。",
    "options": [
      "A. Theodore Roosevelt",
      "B. Woodrow Wilson",
      "C. Franklin Roosevelt",
      "D. Harry S. Truman"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. Franklin Roosevelt"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi8e",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The first group of English settlers went to North America in the year of and named the settlement they set up after.",
    "question_zh": "1607年，首批英国移民抵达北美，并以________命名其建立的定居点。",
    "options": [
      "A. 1607, their king",
      "B. 1620",
      "their home city",
      "C. 1617",
      "their captain",
      "D. 1603",
      "their queen"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. 1607, their king"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifd",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Those that came to the new world from England in 1620 were mainly.",
    "question_zh": "1620年从英国抵达新大陆的人群主要是。",
    "options": [
      "A. debtors",
      "B. pilgrims persecuted in their home country",
      "C. explorers",
      "D. fortune seekers"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. pilgrims persecuted in their home country"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi4x",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "How many states were there at the time of independence of the United States?",
    "question_zh": "美国独立时共有________个州。",
    "options": [
      "A. 13.",
      "B. 18.",
      "C. 35.",
      "D. 48."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. 13."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgijp",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Which of the following was the last continental state added to the Union?",
    "question_zh": "以下哪一州是最后加入联邦的大陆州？",
    "options": [
      "A. Kentucky.",
      "B. Arizona.",
      "C. Oregon.",
      "D. Alaska."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Alaska."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgii2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In his inaugural speech, _____said, \"The only thing we have to fear is fear itself. \"",
    "question_zh": "在其就职演说中，表示：“我们唯一需要恐惧的，就是恐惧本身。”",
    "options": [
      "A. Abraham Lincoln",
      "B. John F. Kennedy",
      "C. Franklin Roosevelt",
      "D. Woodrow Wilson"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. Franklin Roosevelt"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgilr",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The period after WWII, America witnessed a series of social movements, rebellions and changes except _____ .",
    "question_zh": "二战后，美国经历了一系列社会运动、反抗与变革，但________除外。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Equal Rights Movement",
      "B. anti-Vietnam War movement",
      "C. feminist movement",
      "D. the Civil Rights Movement"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. the Equal Rights Movement"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi6d",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Lincoln ended his famous Gettysburg Speech by these words; \"That government _____the people, _____the people, _____the people, shall not perish from the earth. \"",
    "question_zh": "林肯在著名的葛底斯堡演说结尾说道：“民有、民治、民享的政府，从地球上消亡。”",
    "options": [
      "A. to",
      "for",
      "by",
      "B. from",
      "of",
      "for",
      "C. with",
      "of",
      "by",
      "D. of",
      "by",
      "for"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. of; by; for"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifi",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The victory of _____ was the turning point of the War of Independence.",
    "question_zh": "的胜利是独立战争的转折点。",
    "options": [
      "A. Saratoga",
      "B. Gettysburg",
      "C. Trenton",
      "D. Yorktown"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Yorktown"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiaj",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "_____ played an important role in the construction of cross-country railroads in the 1860s.",
    "question_zh": "在19世纪60年代横贯大陆铁路建设中发挥了重要作用。",
    "options": [
      "A. Black Americans",
      "B. Hispanics",
      "C. Chinese laborers",
      "D. Japanese-Americans"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. Chinese laborers"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi93",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "When did the American Civil War break out?",
    "question_zh": "美国南北战争何时爆发？",
    "options": [
      "A. In 1775",
      "B. In 1812",
      "C. In 1861",
      "D. In 1863"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. In 1861"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgib1",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "After the WWI, the US President Woodrow Wilson refused to ratify the ______ which included little of his proposal except the founding of the League of Nations, which was controlled by Britain and France.",
    "question_zh": "一战后，美国总统伍德罗·威尔逊拒绝批准，该条约仅包含其提议的极少内容，除由英法控制的国际联盟外。",
    "options": [
      "A. Treaty of Versailles",
      "B. Declaration of Independence",
      "C. Articles of Confederation",
      "D. Great Compromise of July 16"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Treaty of Versailles"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgicd",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "A historic moment of the civil rights movement was the March on Washington of August 28, 1963 when _____ delivered his speech \"I Have a Dream\".",
    "question_zh": "民权运动的历史性时刻是1963年8月28日的“向华盛顿进军”，当时________发表了“我有一个梦想”演讲。",
    "options": [
      "A. John F. Kennedy",
      "B. President Johnson",
      "C. Martin Luther King Jr.",
      "D. Mario Savio"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. Martin Luther King Jr."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgijx",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The US experienced the longest continuous economic expansion since WWII and the US seemed invincible until terrorist attacks on __________ .",
    "question_zh": "美国经历了二战以来最长的持续经济扩张，直至________遭受恐怖袭击，其不可战胜的表象才被打破。",
    "options": [
      "A. September 11 th , 1991",
      "B. September 11 th , 2001",
      "C. November 9 th, 2001",
      "D. November, 9 th, 1991"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. September 11 th , 2001"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgikn",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Before WWI, America resorted to the _________ which claimed that the Western Hemisphere was its sphere of influence and warned European powers to keep hands off or risk wars.",
    "question_zh": "一战前，美国奉行，宣称西半球为其势力范围，并警告欧洲列强不得干涉，否则将面临战争。",
    "options": [
      "A. Monroe Doctrine",
      "B. Isolationism",
      "C. Open Door Policy",
      "D. Conservatism"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Monroe Doctrine"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi4e",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The British established 13 colonies along _________.",
    "question_zh": "英国沿________建立了13个殖民地。",
    "options": [
      "A. the west coast of North America",
      "B. the west coast of South America",
      "C. the east coast of North America",
      "D. the east coast of South America"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. the east coast of North America"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi37",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The Progressive Movement wanted to ________ in order to stop big business control.",
    "question_zh": "进步运动旨在，以遏制大企业的控制。",
    "options": [
      "A. initiate strict government regulation",
      "B. have the government fix prices",
      "C. break up all the big businesses",
      "D. do away with rebates"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. initiate strict government regulation"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiar",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In American history, the refers to the post-civil War period, known for the sharp contrast between the rich and the poor, for corrupt politics and governments, and for illegal means of big businesses to win huge profits.",
    "question_zh": "在美国历史上，指内战后的时期，以贫富差距悬殊、政治腐败及大企业非法牟取暴利为特征。",
    "options": [
      "A. Modern Age",
      "B. Gilded Age",
      "C. Lost Age",
      "D. Development Age"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Gilded Age"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi3s",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The serious economic crisis in the late 1920s and 1930s was first brought about by _____________.",
    "question_zh": "20世纪20年代末至30年代的严重经济危机最初由________引发。",
    "options": [
      "A. bank failures",
      "B. serious unemployment",
      "C. farm foreclosures",
      "D. the stock market crash"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. the stock market crash"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgibe",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The purpose of the New Deal measures was to __________.",
    "question_zh": "“新政”措施的目的是。",
    "options": [
      "A. save American democracy and the capitalist system",
      "B. check the worsening of the economic situation",
      "C. help people tide over the difficulty",
      "D. increase American export"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. save American democracy and the capitalist system"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi1c",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "On June 5, 1947, ________ suggested that the U.S. should offer economic aid to Western Europe so as to protect the region from Soviet expansion.",
    "question_zh": "1947年6月5日，提议美国应向西欧提供经济援助，以防止该地区受到苏联扩张威胁。",
    "options": [
      "A. George Marshall",
      "B. Franklin D. Roosevelt",
      "C. George Kennan",
      "D. Harry Truman"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. George Marshall"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgii",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The United States of America is the ____________ country in the world in size.",
    "question_zh": "按国土面积计算，美国是世界________大国。",
    "options": [
      "A. largest",
      "B. second-largest",
      "C. third-largest",
      "D. fourth-largest"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. fourth-largest"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi4l",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "____________ extend from the northern tip of Maine southwestern to Alabama.",
    "question_zh": "从缅因州北部延伸至阿拉巴马州西南部。",
    "options": [
      "A. The Rocky Mountains",
      "B. The Appalachian Highlands",
      "C. The Coast Mountains",
      "D. The Blue Mountains"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. The Appalachian Highlands"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi2x",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The climate of the United States is influenced by ____________.",
    "question_zh": "美国气候受________影响。",
    "options": [
      "A. the Atlantic and Pacific Oceans",
      "B. the Gulf of Mexico",
      "C. the Great Lakes",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgiz",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "What is the leading commercial crop of the south?",
    "question_zh": "南部最主要的经济作物是什么？",
    "options": [
      "A. Wheat.",
      "B. Tobacco.",
      "C. Sugar cane.",
      "D. Rice."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Tobacco."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgifq",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "What Midwestern city is the automobile capital of the world?",
    "question_zh": "美国中西部哪座城市是世界汽车工业中心？",
    "options": [
      "A. Chicago.",
      "B. Detroit.",
      "C. Milwaukee.",
      "D. Cleveland."
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Detroit."
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgidd",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "One of the most important lakes in the United States is _________, which is the largest fresh water lake in the world.",
    "question_zh": "美国最重要的湖泊之一是，它是全球最大的淡水湖。",
    "options": [
      "A. Lake Superior",
      "B. Lake Michigan",
      "C. Lake Huron",
      "D. Lake Ontario"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Lake Superior"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi6e",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "New England lies in __________ of the United States.",
    "question_zh": "新英格兰位于美国的。",
    "options": [
      "A. the northern part",
      "B. the southern part",
      "C. the northeastern part",
      "D. the southeastern part"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "C. the northeastern part"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgi3e",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The southern part of the Pacific coast in California has a ___________ climate.",
    "question_zh": "加利福尼亚州太平洋沿岸南部地区属于________气候。",
    "options": [
      "A. subtropical",
      "B. continental desert",
      "C. maritime",
      "D. Mediterranean"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "D. Mediterranean"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgirf",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "The smallest state in the United States is ___________.",
    "question_zh": "美国面积最小的州是。",
    "options": [
      "A. Washington",
      "B. Rhode Island",
      "C. Hawaii",
      "D. Maryland"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "B. Rhode Island"
  },
  {
    "id": "Qmin4zkgipn",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "In the United States, the largest city along the Pacific coast is ___________.",
    "question_zh": "在美国，太平洋沿岸最大的城市是_。",
    "options": [
      "A. Los Angeles",
      "B. San Francisco",
      "C. Seattle",
      "D. Portland"
    ],
    "options_zh": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A. Los Angeles"
  }
]